Problem Statement

You are given an integer, N. Write a program to determine if N is an element of the Fibonacci Sequence.

The first few elements of fibonacci sequence are 0,1,1,2,3,5,8,13,⋯ A fibonacci sequence is one where every element is a sum of the previous two elements in the sequence. The first two elements are 0 and 1.

Formally: 
fib0fib1⋮fibn=0=1=fibn−1+fibn−2∀n>1
Input Format 
The first line contains T, number of test cases. 
T lines follows. Each line contains an integer N.

Output Format 
Display IsFibo if N is a fibonacci number and IsNotFibo if it is not a fibonacci number. The output for each test case should be displayed in a new line.

Constraints 
1≤T≤105 
1≤N≤1010
Sample Input

3
5
7
8
Sample Output

IsFibo
IsNotFibo
IsFibo
Explanation 
5 is a Fibonacci number given by fib5=3+2 
7 is not a Fibonacci number 
8 is a Fibonacci number given by fib6=5+3