Problem Statement

Sorting 
One common task for computers is to sort data. For example, people might want to see all their files on a computer sorted by size. Since sorting is a simple problem with many different possible solutions, it is often used to introduce the study of algorithms.

Insertion Sort 
These challenges will cover Insertion Sort, a simple and intuitive sorting algorithm. We will first start with an already sorted list.

Insert element into sorted list 
Given a sorted list with an unsorted number V in the right-most cell, can you write some simple code to insert V into the array so it remains sorted?

Print the array every time a value is shifted in the array until the array is fully sorted. The goal of this challenge is to follow the correct order of insertion sort.

Guideline: You can copy the value of V to a variable, and consider its cell "empty". Since this leaves an extra cell empty on the right, you can shift everything over until V can be inserted. This will create a duplicate of each value, but when you reach the right spot, you can replace a value with V.

Input Format 
There will be two lines of input:

s - the size of the array
ar - the sorted array of integers
Output Format 
On each line, output the entire array every time an item is shifted in it.

Constraints 
1<=s<=1000 
-10000<=x<= 10000, x ∈ ar

Sample Input

5
2 4 6 8 3
Sample Output

2 4 6 8 8 
2 4 6 6 8 
2 4 4 6 8 
2 3 4 6 8 
Explanation

3 is removed from the end of the array.
In the 1st line 8 > 3, 8 is shifted one cell right. 
In the 2nd line 6 > 3, 6 is shifted one cell right. 
In the 3rd line 4 > 3, 4 is shifted one cell right. 
In the 4th line 2 < 3, 3 is placed at position 2.

Task

Complete the method insertionSort which takes in 1 parameter:

ar - an array with the value V in the right-most cell.